megamarketingtools.com 2012-06-23

# Wealth Group International- Spam Policy

Wealth Group International Inc.operates multiple web sites including Marketingtools4u.com, Adprotiser.com,MegaListBuilderPro.com, MegaSplashPage.com, MegaMarketingTools.com, Buzzwah.com HostingMMT.com and MegaTraffic4U.com. All policies and statements in this privacy policy are intended to apply to all Wealth Group International Inc.services. 

Wealth Group International Inc.is committed to protecting your privacy. 

Wealth Group International Inc.will never willfully disclose personally identifiable information about its customers to any third party without first receiving that customer's permission, unless necessary for legal reasons. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to admin@megamarketingtools.com. 

What information does Wealth Group International Inc.Collect?   
You don't need to provide any information in order to browse web sites in our network. 

If you choose to subscribe to any of our services (become a member), you could be asked to provide the following information: name, company name, email address, city, state, country, zip code, phone number.

Marketingtools4u.com will ask for your social security number or ein number if you wish to sell products from this paticular site. This is in accordance with laws governing the USA. 

We will NOT disclose, sell or exchange any member's personally identifiable information to or with anyone, without your approval. The only circumstances under which personally identifiable information about Wealth Group International Inc.members will be shared in a manner inconsistent to that stated above is if we believe disclosure is reasonably necessary to:   
comply with the law or legal process;  
protect or defend the rights or property of Wealth Group International Inc.or others;  
enforce our Terms of Service; or  
respond to claims that the content of any communication on our network violates the rights of others.

If you complete any of our online forms (including forms on third party advertiser sites) requesting information regarding any of our offers or offers from any of our members, your information will be provided to our members. You will have the option to confirm or decline any offer sent to you by any of our members through our network by clicking on either an authorization link or a remove link. 

Once you confirm any such offer the privacy policies and standards of our members will vary and may be significantly different from the policies posted here and in use by Wealth Group International Inc. 

##### How does Wealth Group International Inc.use the information collected?

We will aggregate member and visitor information and perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our members and visitors, to measure overall demographics and interests regarding specific areas of our network and to analyze how and where to use our resources. We also use the aggregate data collected to inform our sponsors and members as to the number of people who have seen and "clicked" on their advertisement, requested further information, or have responded to any offer provided by our members via our network. In addition, Wealth Group International Inc.may compile and disclose aggregate information about its visitors and members for promotional or other purposes. For example, we might want to disclose that a certain percentage of our members are located within a particular geographic area or fall within a particular age range. 

##### Does Wealth Group International Inc. use cookies?

Wealth Group International Inc.uses both session cookies and persistent cookies (for an explanation of cookies, please see http://www.epic.org/privacy/internet/cookies/). Cookies help us determine how long visitors view particular content, which particular content (e.g., advertising) visitors view, which content or sites visitors link to, and which of our services members and visitors use. 

Persistent cookies are randomly generated and uniquely assigned to each visitor. They are not associated with any personally identifiable information such as name or password. 

Session cookies help us keep track of when a person is logged in. Once a member is logged in, session cookies allow us to personalize information on our Web site for them, as well as keep track of areas to which they have membership privileges. 

##### How can I change or delete information about me stored at Wealth Group International Inc.?

As a registered Wealth Group International Inc.member, you have easy access to your information, along with the ability to change it. And, you can always choose to unsubscribe from any services you've subscribed to at any of our sites. 

##### I am not a member. I am receiving emails from your members. How can I unsubscribe from email lists at Megalistbuilderpro.com?

There are three ways to unsubscribe from Wealth Group International Inc. mailinglists: 

  1. Use the unsubscribe link that appears at the bottom of every message you receive from any of our lists. Clicking the link automatically unsbuscribes you from the list your email came from. **Clicking this option will remove and ban your email address from future use in our network.**    

  2. Send an email to [admin@Megalistbuilderpro.com](mailto:admin@Megalistbuilderpro.com) with the message" _UNSUBSCRIBE {_ youremail@email.com} from Megalistbuilderpro.com" in the subject line.  
Your address will be manually removed from our system within ten business days. 
  3.  Or you can Mail your request to our offices at  
**Wealth Group International Inc.  
848 N. Rainbow Blvd.  
Suite 2541  
Las Vegas, NV 89107**  

##### How does Wealth Group International Inc. protect the privacy of children?

The Wealth Group International Inc.services are not intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. However, as with any Web site, children can access all parts of the site which are accessible to the general public. See the "What information does Wealth Group International Inc. collect?" section of this document for an explanation of what information is publicly accessible through the Wealth Group International Inc. sites. 

##### Notification of Changes

If Wealth Group International Inc.intends to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect visitor or member information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying visitors of the change. In some cases when we post such a notice we will also email users who have opted to receive communications from us notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please contact us.  
Support at megamarketingtools.com or mail us at   
Wealth Group international Inc. 848 N. Rainbow Blvd.Suite 2541 Las Vegas, NV 89107

Wealth Group International Inc.
